Kalyani Vajpayee

Senior HR Execuitve

An HR professional with 5 + Years of experience.

Oversee well-organized and efficient HR operations by balancing organizational targets with compliance and employee demands. Focused on maximizing resource utilization and enhancing performance with forward-thinking approaches. Solid background of improving collaboration and consensus across different industries and company environments.

Work History

2021-04

2019-09 - Senior HR Executive

Circuit Systems India Limited, Ahmedabad, Gujarat Majorly looked after recruitment for their new office at Ahmedabad using RMS.

Also have recruitment experience for USA Office which is situated in California USA.

Managed whole employee life cycle.

Also handled administration for the same.

Also managed marketing for PCB Power Market India.

2017-02 - Ambica Polymer

2019-03 Managed whole employee life cycle of 200.

Put all my efforts to maintain Human Resource

Department

Recruitment of blue collars and managing their life cycle was a major role.

2015-06 - Assistant Manager Human Resource

Radiant Heat Exchangers Pvt. Ltd, Pune, Maharashtra Majorly looked after 350 staff on following verticals.

Recruitment and Induction

Training and Development

Competency Mapping

Performance Appraisal

Compensation and Benefit

Employee Engagement and Reward and Recognition

Full and Final procedure

Contact

Address

Ahmedabad , Gujarat, 382470

Phone

+91-8319725731

E-mail

kalyani2406@gmail.com

Skills

Recruitment

Salary administration

Employee engagement

Performance management

Audit Support

Training solutions development

MS Office

Process improvements

Documentation and reporting

Policy and procedure modification

Compliance

ISO (Certification + Surveillance Audits)

0001-01 - HR Intern

2014-10 ACG ACPL

 Analyzing the effectiveness of on-going employee engagement activities and Recommendation at ACG-ACPL (Made and Implemented Buddy Policy).

2011-06 - BE Intern

2012-01 Linux Solutions Pvt. Ltd

 Analysis and enhancement of AD-HOC Network Protocol through NCTUNs.

Education

2008-09 - B.E: I.T

2012-06 Radharaman Institute of Technology And Science -

Bhopal

GPA: 76.37

2013-06 - MBA: PM & HRD

2015-04 Shri Balaji Society - Pune

GPA: 73

2013-06 - MLL & LW : Labor Law

2015-04 Balaji Law College - Pune

Additional Information

Coming to extra curricular activities.

Got First prize in short put

Played handball at National Level.

Reading

Story Books and personality improvement books i have read.

Also have a habit of reading magazine like Corporate Citizen to be in touch with Human Resource Industry.